{
    "id": "4f845f22315b4a088aa287dc515d426d",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was ..................................... anything in the box.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "almost",
                "nearly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ................................... books lying on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a few",
                "the few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Standing",
                "Stood"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind .................................. a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "moving",
                "to move"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There .................................... two hundred children watching the game.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not ......................................... the meeting on Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attend",
                "to attend"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He used ........................................ poems when he was a student.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "writing",
                "to write",
                "to writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. have bought it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't need",
                "needn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ........................................ any other Christmas gift I have ever had.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "better then",
                "the best",
                "better than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ....................................... plays for television.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not write",
                "do not write",
                "does not write"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}